Keisha Subaldo

Iloilo City, Probinsya sang Iloilo keishamaevsubaldo4_3kn@indeedemail.com +63 961 120 9695

Experienced Head with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital, community, health care & business industry. Skilled in Health

Promotion, Nutritional Counseling, Nutrition Education, Clinical

Nutrition, Dietetics, Food Safety and Food Service Management. Strong

healthcare services & operations professional with a Bachelor of

Science on Nutrtition Dietetics, Wellness and Health with a lots of Diploma & short courses on

Marketing, Business, Hotel and Facilities

Management, Nutrition, Food and Culinary Arts for Nutritionist

Dietitians.

Work Experience

Registered Nutritionist Dietitian

Professional Marketing Insights Inc. - Iloilo City May 2021 to February 2022

I have 8 years and 10 months of total experienced as NUTRITIONIST DIETITIAN in my profession field.

Field Registered Nutritionist Dietitian/Nutrition Advocate

TEAM ONGROUND INC - Iloilo City November 2020 to April 2021

Field Enumerator

Philippine Statistics Authority - Iloilo City October 2020 to November 2020

Registered Nutritionist Dietitian

Abbott Company - Iloilo City September 2019 to September 2020

Clinical Dietetic Coordinator

Compass Catering Services W.L.L. - Al-Wakrah March 2017 to August 2019

Pioneer Head Dietitian

Qualimed Hospital iloilo - Iloilo City September 2014 to March 2017

Registered Nutritionist Dietitian

Diet & Nutrition AVI NESTLE PHILIPPINES January 2013 to February 2017

Wellness Program Project by Nestle Philippines "Choose Wellness Choose Nestle"

Staff Dietitian

St. Therese MTTC HOSPITAL ILOILO - Iloilo City January 2014 to August 2014

Education

Diploma in Fundamentals Health Coaching and Nutrition & Professional Weight Course

Health Sciences Academy at UK 2020

Secondary Education

University of Iloilo

Bachelor of Science in Nutrition and Dietetics in Nutrition and Dietetics

University of San Agustin

Skills

Digital Marketing Sales
Telemarketing Sales
Microsoft Proficient
Photography
Video Maker
Menu Logistics
Cerner
Powe Chart
Food Service
Wellness and Life Coach
Food Safety and Hygiene
Food Service Management
Clinical Nutrition
Nutrition Educator and Councelor

Links

https://www.credly.com/users/keisha-mae-subaldo/badges

https://www.linkedin.com/in/keisha-mae-v-s-a7475b12a